http://xmlvalidation.com/privacy

ValidateDocumentationAn exampleAboutPrivacy
Privacy Policy
Change privacy settings
1. An overview of data protection
General The following gives a simple overview of what happens to your personal information when you visit our website. Personal information is any data with which you could be personally identified. Detailed information on the subject of data protection can be found in our privacy policy found below.
Data collection on our website Who is responsible for the data collection on this website?
The data collected on this website are processed by the website operator. The operator's contact details can be found in the website's required legal notice.
How do we collect your data? Some data are
collected when you provide it to us. This could, for example, be xml files you upload.
Other data are collected automatically by our IT systems when you visit the website. These data are primarily technical data such as the browser and operating system you are using or when you accessed the page. These data are collected automatically as soon as you enter our website.
What do we use your data for?
Part of the data is collected to ensure the proper functioning of the website.
Uploaded XML files or schema files are used for validating them. No files you upload are stored persistently on our servers. They are only kept in memory for the duration of your session so that you can upload multiple files that reference each other. None of the files you upload are used for any purpose which does
not serve the functioning of this website. In particular, they are not shared with third parties.
Other data can be used to analyze how visitors use the site. What rights do you have regarding your data? You always have the right to request information about your stored data, its origin, its recipients, and the purpose of its collection at no charge. You also have the right to request that it be corrected, blocked, or deleted. You can contact us at any time using the address given in the legal notice if you have further questions about the issue of privacy and data protection. You may also, of course, file a complaint with the competent regulatory authorities.
2. General information and mandatory information
Data protection The operators of this website take the protection of your personal data very seriously. We treat your personal data as confidential and in accordance with the statutory data protection regulations and this privacy policy. If you use this website, various pieces of personal data will be collected. Personal information is any data with which you could be personally identified. This privacy policy explains what information we collect and what we use it for. It also explains how and for what purpose this happens. Please note that data transmitted via the internet (e.g. via email communication) may be subject to security breaches. Complete protection of your data from third-party access is not possible.
Notice concerning the party responsible for this website The party responsible for processing data on this website is: Theano GmbH
Kiefernweg 8
49205 Hasbergen
Deutschland
Telephone: +49-5405-92825432
Email:
The responsible party is the natural or legal person who alone or jointly with others decides on the purposes and means of processing personal data (names, email addresses, etc.).
Revocation of your consent to the processing of your data Many data processing operations are only possible with your express consent. You may revoke your consent at any time with future effect. An informal email making this request is sufficient. The data processed before we receive your request may still be legally processed.
Right to file complaints with regulatory authorities If there has been a breach of data protection legislation, the person affected may file a complaint with the competent regulatory authorities. The competent regulatory authority for matters related to data protection legislation is the data protection officer of the German state in which our company is headquartered. A list of data protection officers and their contact details can be found at the following link: https://www.bfdi.bund.de/DE/Infothek/Anschriften_Links/anschriften_links-node.html.
SSL or TLS encryption This site uses SSL or TLS encryption for security reasons and for the protection of the transmission of confidential content, such as the inquiries you send to us as the site operator. You can recognize an encrypted connection in your browser's address line when it changes
from "http://" to "https://" and the lock icon is displayed in your browser's address bar. If SSL or TLS encryption is activated, the data you transfer to us cannot be read by third parties. Should it ever not be activated, please activate it by changing the "http" to "https" in the address field.
Information, blocking, deletion As permitted by law, you have the right to be provided at any time with information free of charge about any of your personal data that is stored as well as its origin, the recipient and the purpose for which it has been processed. You also have the right to have this data corrected, blocked or deleted. You can contact us at any time using the address given in our legal notice if you have further questions on the topic of personal data.
Opposition to promotional emails We hereby expressly prohibit the use of contact data published in the context of website legal notice requirements with regard to sending promotional and informational materials not expressly requested. The website operator reserves the right to take specific legal action if unsolicited advertising material, such as email spam, is received.
3. Data protection officer
Statutory data protection officer If you want a quick reply to a data protection-related request, please send a mail to:
. But you are also free to contact our external data protection officer.
Data protection officer:
Legaltrust GmbH
Contact person: Herr Michael Michalak
Lietzenburger Str. 94
10719 Berlin
Germany
Tel. 030 / 887 27 609
Fax. 030 / 887 27 606
E-Mail: datenschutz@prive.eu
4. Data collection on our website
Cookies Some of our web pages use cookies. Cookies do not harm your computer and do not contain any viruses. Cookies help make our website more user-friendly, efficient, and secure. Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer and saved by your browser. Most of the cookies we use are so-called "session cookies." They are automatically deleted after your visit. Other cookies remain in your device's memory until you delete them. These cookies make it possible to recognize your browser when you next visit the site. You can configure your browser to inform you about the use of cookies so that you can decide on a case-by-case basis whether to accept or reject a cookie. Alternatively, your browser can be configured to automatically accept cookies under certain conditions or to always reject them, or to automatically delete cookies when closing your browser. Disabling cookies may limit the functionality of this website. Cookies which are necessary to allow electronic communications or to provide certain functions you wish to use (such as the shopping cart) are stored pursuant to Art. 6 paragraph 1, letter f of DSGVO. The website operator has a legitimate interest in the storage of cookies to ensure an optimized service provided free of technical errors. If other cookies (such as those used to analyze your surfing behavior) are also stored, they will be treated separately in this privacy policy.
Server log files The website provider automatically collects and stores information that your browser automatically transmits to us in "server log files". These are:
Browser type and browser version Operating system used Referrer URL Host name of the accessing computer Time of the server request IP address
These data will not be combined with data from other sources. The basis for data processing is Art. 6 (1) (b) DSGVO, which allows the processing of data to fulfill a contract or for measures preliminary to a contract.
Data transferred when signing up for services and digital content We transmit personally identifiable data to third parties only to the extent required to fulfill the terms of your contract with us, for example, to banks entrusted to process your payments. Your data will not be transmitted for any other purpose unless you have given your express permission to do so. Your data will not be disclosed to third parties for advertising purposes without your express consent. The basis for data processing is Art. 6 (1) (b) DSGVO, which allows the processing of data to fulfill a contract or for measures preliminary to a contract.
5. Analytics and advertising
Matomo (formerly Piwik) This website uses the open source web analytics service Matomo. Matomo uses so-called "cookies". These are text files that are stored on your computer and that allow an analysis of the use of the website by you. For this purpose, the information generated by the cookie about the use of this website is stored on our server. The IP address is anonymized before it is stored. Matomo cookies remain on your device until you delete them. The storage of Matomo cookies is based on Art. 6 (1) (f) DSGVO. The website operator has a legitimate interest in analyzing user behavior in order to optimize both its website and its advertising. The information generated by the cookies about your use of this website will not be disclosed to third parties. You can prevent these cookies being stored by selecting the appropriate settings in your browser. However, we wish to point out that doing so may mean you will not be able to enjoy the full functionality of this website. If you do not agree with the storage and use of your data, you can disable this feature here. In this case, an opt-out cookie will be stored in your browser to prevent Matomo from storing your usage data. If you delete your cookies, this will mean that the opt-out cookie will also be deleted. You will then need to reactivate it when you return to our site if you wish your activity not to be tracked.
Google AdSense This website uses Google AdSense, a service for including advertisements from Google Inc. ("Google"). It is operated by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA. Google AdSense uses so-called "cookies", which are text files stored in your computer that enable an analysis of the way you use the website. Google AdSense also uses so-called web beacons (invisible graphics). Through these web beacons, information such as the visitor traffic on these pages can be evaluated. The information generated by cookies and web beacons relating to your use of this website (including your IP address), and delivery of advertising formats, is transmitted to a Google server in the US and stored there. This information can be passed on from Google to contracting parties of Google. However, Google will not merge your IP address with other data you have stored. AdSense cookies are stored based on Art. 6 (1) (f) DSGVO. The website operator has a legitimate interest in analyzing user behavior to optimize both its website and its advertising. You can prevent the installation of cookies by setting your browser software accordingly. Please be aware that in this case, you may not be able to make full use of all the features of this website. By using this website, you agree to the processing of data relating to you and collected by Google as described and for the purposes set out above.
Yieldlove
We also use Yieldlove as advertising partner. In the Yieldlove section below, "we" refers to Yieldlove, not Theano GmbH.
Yieldlove
delivers advertising banners on behalf of its customers. All our
banners use cookies. We place these banners on third-party websites,
such as a news page, with the help of third-party providers.
For
diagnostic purposes, troubleshooting, and detecting fraudulent
behavior, we collect user information in cookies using our 6-month
lifecycle. The captured user information includes user agent, device,
HTTP referrer and the IP. This data is not retained for more than 7
days.
Yieldlove
takes reasonable steps to protect any information we process from
misuse, loss, unauthorized access, modification or notification. We
take physical, electronic and procedural security measures to protect
the data we process. By doing so, we restrict access to this
information to authorized employees.
For
the cookies that our third-party advertisers place for advertising
purposes, we refer to the disclaimers that they have provided on the
topic on their own websites. Note that we can only refer to these
disclaimers, as they change regularly and Yieldlove has no control
over them.
THIRD
PARTIES AND OPT-OUT
A
central contradiction possibility for different third-party suppliers
in particular US-companies is also attainable under the following
link: optout.networkadvertising.org But you can also opt-out
separately for each company we work with. Responsible for the data
collection and for the delivery of interest based-based online
advertising are the following companies on behalf of Yieldlove GmbH:
4w
Marketplace
4w
Marketplace (www.4wmarketplace.com) uses technologies, to show
interest-based advertising to you. Provider of 4w Marketplace is 4w
Marketplace srl located in Fisciano (Salerno) – 84084 in Via
Giovanni Paolo II n.100. In case you would like to prevent 4w
Marketplace from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the
opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered
information until now and prevents it from collecting any information
in the future.
Privacy
policy:
http://www.4wmarketplace.com/privacy/
Opt-out:
Wildersgade 10B, 1, 1408 Copenhagen, Denmark. In case you would like
to prevent Adform from gathering anonymised data you can do so by
using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all
gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any
information in the future.
Privacy
policy:
https://site.adform.com/privacy-policy-opt-out/
Opt-out:
https://site.adform.com/privacy-policy-opt-out/
Amazon
Amazon
(https://www.aps.amazon.com) uses technologies, to show
interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Amazon publisher
services is Amazon publisher services located in Washington – 410
Terry Ave. North, Seattle, WA 98109-5210. In case you would like to
prevent Amazon publisher services from gathering anonymised data you
can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie
deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from
collecting any information in the future.
Privacy
policy:
https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html/ref=hp_left_sib?ie=UTF8&nodeId=468496
Opt-out:
https://www.amazon.com/adprefs/ref=hp_468496_advertisingpref2
AppNexus
AppNexus
(https://www.appnexus.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based
advertising to you. Provider of AppNexus is AppNexus Group located in
in New York – 28 W. 23rd
Street, New York, New York, 10010. In
case you would like to prevent Appnexus from gathering anonymised
data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out
cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it
from collecting any information in the future.
Privacy
policy: https://www.appnexus.com/en/company/privacy-policy
Opt-out:
https://www.appnexus.com/en/company/platform-privacy-policy#choices
Conversant
Conversant
(https://www.conversantmedia.com) uses technologies, to show
interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Conversant is
Conversant inc. located in in Chicago (IL) – 101 North Wacker, 23rd
Floor Chicago, IL 60606. In case you would like to prevent
Conversant from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the
opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered
information until now and prevents it from collecting any information
in the future.
Privacy
policy: http://www.conversantmedia.com/legal/privacy
Opt-out:
http://optout.conversantmedia.com/
Criteo
Criteo
(https://www.criteo.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based
advertising to you. Provider of Criteo is Criteo located in Paris –
32 Rue Blanche – 75009 Paris - France. In case you would like to
prevent Criteo from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using
the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered
information until now and prevents it from collecting any information
in the future.
Privacy
policy: http://www.criteo.com/privacy/
Opt-out:
https://www.criteo.com/privacy/
District
M
District
M (https://districtm.net) uses technologies, to show interest-based
advertising to you. Provider of District M is District M located in
Montreal – 5455 Gaspe Ave #730, Montreal, QC H2T 3B3, Canada. In
case you would like to prevent District M from gathering anonymised
data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out
cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it
from collecting any information in the future.
Privacy
policy:
https://districtm.net/en/page/platforms-data-and-privacy-policy/
Opt-out:
https://cdn.districtm.ca/optout.html
Doubleclick
Doubleclick
(www.doubleclickbygoogle.com) uses technologies, to show
interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Doubleclick is Google
located in Ireland Limited, Gordon House, Barrow St Dublin 4 Ireland.
In
case you would like to prevent Doubleclick from gathering anonymised
data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out
cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it
from collecting any information in the future.
Privacy
policy: http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/
Opt-out:
https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated?hl=en
Facebook
Facebook
(www.facebook.com)
uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you.
Provider of Facebook is Facebook Inc., located in 1601 S. California
Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA. In case you would like to prevent
Facebook from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the
opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered
information until now and prevents it from collecting any information
in the future.
Privacy
policy: www.facebook.com/full_data_use_policy
Opt-out:
www.facebook.com/ads/preferences
Indexexchange
Indexexchange
(www.indexexchange.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based
advertising to you. Provider of Indexexchange is Indexexchange
located in New York – 20 W 22nd
St. Suite 1101, New York, NY
10010. In case you would like to prevent Indexexchange from gathering
anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This
Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and
prevents it from collecting any information in the future.
Privacy
policy: http://www.indexexchange.com/privacy/
Opt-out:
http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/
Media.net
Media.net
(http://www.media.net/privacy-policy) uses technologies, to show
interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Media.net is Media.net
Advertising Ltd. located in Dubai – 107/108, DIC Building 5, Dubai
Internet City, Dubai, 215028, United Arab Emirates. In case you would
like to prevent Media.net from gathering anonymised data you can do
so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all
gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any
information in the future.
Privacy
policy: http://www.media.net/privacy-policy
Opt-out:
http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/
Oath
Oath
(https://www.oath.com/) uses technologies, to show interest-based
advertising to you. Provider of Oath is Oath (EMEA) Limited located
in Dublin - 5-7 Point Square, North Wall Quay. In case you would like
to prevent Oath from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using
the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered
information until now and prevents it from collecting
any information in the future.
Privacy
policy:
http://privacy.aol.com/
Opt-out:
https://aim.yahoo.com/aim/ie/en/optout/
OpenX
OpenX
(https://www.OpenX.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based
advertising to you. Provider of OpenX is OpenX located in Pasadena –
888 E Walnut St, 2nd Floor, Pasadena CA, 91101, USA. In case you
would like to prevent OpenX from gathering anonymised data you can do
so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all
gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any
information in the future.
Privacy
policy: https://www.openx.com/de_de/privacy-policy/
Opt-out:
https://www.openx.com/legal/interest-based-advertising/
Pubmatic
Pubmatic
(https://www.pubmatic.com) uses
technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of
Pubmatic is Pubmatic, Inc. located
in
Redwood City – 305 Main Street, First Floor, Redwood City,
California 94063, USA. In
case you would like to prevent
Pubmatic from
gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link
below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now
and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.
Privacy
policy: https://www.openx.com/de_de/privacy-policy/
Opt-out:
https://pubmatic.com/legal/opt-out/
Pulsepoint
Pulsepoint
(https://www.pulsepoint.com) uses
technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of
Pulsepoint is Pulsepoint, Inc. located
in
New York – 360 Madison Avenue, 14th Floor, New York, NY 10017. In
case you would like to prevent
Pulsepoint from
gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link
below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now
and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.
Privacy
policy: https://www.pulsepoint.com/privacy-policy
Opt-out:
http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/
Reachnet
Reachnet
(https://www.reachnet.de) uses
technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of
gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link
below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now
and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.
Privacy
policy: http://www.reachnet.de/unternehmen/agb.html
Opt-out:
technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of
Rubicon Project is Rubicon Project, inc. located
in
Playa Vista – 12181 Bluff Creek Drive, 4th Floor, Playa Vista, CA
90094, USA. In
case you would like to prevent
Rubicon Project from
gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link
below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now
and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.
Privacy
policy: http://www.rubiconproject.com/privacy-policy/
Opt-out:
https://rubiconproject.com/privacy/consumer-online-profile-and-opt-out/
Primis
Primis
(https://www.primis.tech) uses
technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of
Primis is Primis LTD located
in
622 Third avenue, McCann New York House 10017 New York City, USA. In
case you would like to prevent
Primis from
gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link
below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now
and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.
Privacy
policy:
https://www.primis.tech/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/primisPrivacyPolicy2018.pdf
Opt-out:
https://web.archive.org/web/20180116234711/http:/live.sekindo.com/utils/cookieOptOut.php
Smaato
Smaato
(https://www.smaato.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based
advertising to you. Provider of Smaato is Smaato Ad Services located
in Hamburg – Valentinskamp 70, Emporio, 20355 Hamburg, Germany. In
case you would like to prevent Smaato from gathering anonymised data
you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie
deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from
collecting any information in the future.
Privacy
policy: https://www.smaato.com/privacy/
Opt-out:
http://www.youronlinechoices.eu
SmartAdserver
SmartAdserver
(https://www.smartadserver.com) uses technologies, to show
interest-based advertising to you. Provider of SmartAdserver is
SmartAdserver located in Paris – 66 Rue de la Chaussée d´Antin,
75009 Paris, France. In case you would like to prevent SmartAdserver
from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out
link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information
until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the
future.
Privacy
policy: http://smartadserver.com/company/privacy-policy/
Opt-out:
http://www.smartadserver.com/diffx/optout/IABOptout.aspx
Sovrn
Sovrn
(https://www.sovrn.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based
advertising to you. Provider of Sovrn is Sovrn Holdings, Inc. located
in Boulder – 5541 Central Avenue, Boulder, CO 80301. In case you
would like to prevent Sovrn from gathering anonymised data you can do
so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all
gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any
information in the future.
Privacy
policy: https://www.sovrn.com/privacy-policy-eu/
Opt-out:
interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Ströer SSP is Ströer
media Deutschland GmbH located in Köln – 50999 Köln, Ströer-Allee
1. In case you would like to prevent Adscale from gathering
anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This
Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and
prevents it from collecting any information in the future.
Privacy
policy: http://www.adscale.de/datenschutz
Opt-out:
ih.adscale.de/adscale-ih/oo
Twiago
Twiago
(https://www.twiago.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based
advertising to you. Provider of Twiago is Twiago located in Köln –
Gustav-Heinemann-Ufer 72b, 50968 Köln. In case you would like to
prevent Twiago from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using
the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered
information until now and prevents it from collecting any information
in the future.
Privacy
policy:
http://www.twiago.com/datenschutz/
Opt-out:
http://control.twiago.com/privacy.php?lang=0
Mopub
Mopub
(https://www.mopub.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based
advertising to you. Provider of Mopub is Twitter, Inc. located in San
Francisco – 1355 Market Street, Suite 900, San Francisco, Ca 94103.
In case you would like to prevent Moppub from gathering anonymised
data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out
cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it
from collecting any information in the future.
Privacy
policy:
https://www.mopub.com/legal/privacy/
Opt-out:
https://www.mopub.com/legal/privacy/
Inmobi
Inmobi
(https://www.inmobi.com)
uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you.
Provider of Inmobi is Inmobi Pte Ltd located in Bangalore – Embassy
Tech Square, Kadubeesanahalli Village Outer Ring Road, Varthur Hobli,
Bangalore 560103. In case you would like to prevent Inmobi from
gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link
below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now
and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.
Privacy
policy: https://www.inmobi.com/privacy-policy/
Opt-out:
https://www.inmobi.com/page/opt-out/
OTHER
/ UNFORESEEN COOKIES
Due
to the way in which Internet and websites work, it is possible that
we do not always have oversight into the cookies that are placed
through our banners by third parties. This is particularly the case
when our banners contain embedded elements such as texts, documents,
images or film clips that are stored by another party, but that are
shown on, in or through our banners.
Should
you encounter cookies on this website that fall into this category
which we have not mentioned above, please let us know or contact the
third party directly and ask which cookies they have placed, what the
reason for this is, what the lifetime of the cookie is and in what
way they have safeguarded your privacy.
YOUR
RIGHTS WITH REGARDS TO YOUR DATA
Yieldlove does not view the banner
advertising data it uses as personal data under the applicable law.
Likewise, we do not collect or process sensitive personal data such
as data on racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or
philosophical beliefs, trade union membership, health, or sex life.
We also do not knowingly collect data from children under the age of
12.
However,
if you want to correct, update or delete the banner advertising data
we have, or if you would like to correct, update or delete the
personal data that you have provided to us via the contact form on
our homepage, you can contact us by e-mail at datenschutzbeauftragter@stroeer.de.
EDAA
We
participate in the European Digital Advertising Alliance (EDAA)
self-regulatory programs and adhere to the EDAA
Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising.
EDAA principally acts as the central licensing body for the OBA Icon
and provides technical means for consumers to exercise transparency
and control over OBA through the youronlinechoices.eu online consumer
choice platform. EDAA is governed by EU-level organisations which
make up the value chain of OBA within Europe and acts to ensure
European consistency in approach. Click here to
learn more about the EDAA.
MODIFICATIONS
AND CONTACT
We
will, on occasion need to adapt these statements. For instance, if we
modify our website or if the rules governing cookies or privacy
change. We or our partners may always modify the content of the
statements and the cookies that are stated without prior warning.
Please refer back to this web page to see the latest version.
In
case you have any questions and/or comments, or wish to make a
complaint, please contact us by e-mail at datenschutzbeauftragter@stroeer.de or
by writing to:
